Zack, Arnold Additional Arbitration Cases 6049
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Arnold Zack Additional Arbitration Cases
1995
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Zack, Arnold
6049
9 cubic feet
9 linear ft.
Papers.
5771345
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 14, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 18, 2015
Biographical / Historical
Lawyer, arbitrator, and government official; LLB Yale, 1956, MBA Harvard, 1961, MA Harvard, 1963.
Arnold Marshall Zack is an arbitrator and mediator. Beginning his labor career as a part-time election examiner for the National Labor Relations Board and as a case analyst for the U.S. Wage Stabilization Board (1950-1953), he was also a lecturer in labor economics at Simmons College, Northeastern University (1957-1963); an assistant to Saul Wallen, arbitrator, (1956-1960); director of the Labor-Management Institute of the American Academy of Arbitrators (1966-1968); and has served in various labor-related international posts for the United States government.
Other governmental service includes membership on panels for the Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service, the Massachusetts Public Employment Relations Board, the New York State Public Employment Relations Board, The New Jersey Public Employment Relations Board, The New York City Office of Collective Bargaining, and The National Mediation Board. Zack is also a panel member of the American Arbitration Association, and has served as the permanent arbitrator for a number of major corporations and unions and for the State of New York and the U.S. Postal Service.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Zack, Arnold
5771345
- Bermuda April, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Brown University/SEIU Local 134 Providence, RI (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Brown University/SEIU 134 Providence, RI (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Chesapeake Hardwood/UFW 170 Hancock, VT Nov 15, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Clarkstown/Teachers Assoc. Elmsford, NY Nov 22, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Coca Cola/UFCW Bangor, ME Oct 26, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Cumberland/FOP Lodge 14 Providence, RI Nov - March, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Danvers/AFSCME 93 Danvers Town Hall Dec 19, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Eastern Utilities/UWNE 335 Newport, RI Oct 23, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Hampden County/IBCO Local 248 Ludlow, MA Oct 20, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- HNS Local 426 Amalgamated Transit AAA E. Hartford, CT Nov 27, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Hudson/AFSCME 93 Oct 13, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Hudson AFSCME 93 Hudson, MA Town Hall June 7, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- IRS/NTEU Sept 20-21, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- IRS/NTEU April 18 Andover, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Kearsarge SD/Education Assoc. Factfinding May 2, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Leominster/IAFF Leominster, MA June 5, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Lynnfield/AFSCME 93 Lynnfield, MA May 16, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Manchester/FF 856 Manchester, NH May 15, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Manchester July 18, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Marathon, Inc./SEIU 254 AAA Boston Aug 22, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Natick Paperboard/UPIU Holiday Inn, Natick June 6, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- New England Wooden Ware/UPIU Westminster, MA May 17, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- NE Woodenware/UPIU 818 Westminster, MA Nov 29, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- N. Fairfield/Board of ED N. Fairfield, CT Nov 17, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- NH State Employees Mediation Dec 12-14, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- PA Power & Light Co/IBEW 1600 Allentown, PA Aug 24, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- City of Philadelphia/IAFF 22 AAA Phil (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Plymouth/AFSCME 93 Plymouth, MA Oct 10, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Town of Plymouth/AFSCME 93 Plymouth, MA Dec 11, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Exeter FF Assoc. and Town of Exeter Jan 1 - Dec 31, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Triborough Bridge & Tunnel (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Tri-Borough Bridge and Tunnel Officers Association Comparative Compensation Report, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Tri-Borough Bridge and Tunnel Association (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Mayor's Advisory Committee on Police Management and Personnel Policy Final Report Volume III Supporting Documents (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Misc. (Box 2, Folder 6)
- NYS PERB about TBTA and TOBTA (Box 2, Folder 7)
- TBTA and Notes (Box 2, Folder 8)
- NYS PERB TBTA and BTOBA March 27, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- NYS PERB TBTA and BTOBA (Box 2, Folder 10)
- TBTA and BTOBA (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Shaw's/UFCW 791 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Sullivan County Nursing/AFSCME April 8, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Westfield Gas/IBEW 455 Holyoke, MA, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  April 26
- City of Medford Police Assoc. City Hall Dec 6, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- NASHUA/AFSCME 365 April 17, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- N. Britain SD/Fed. Of Teachers Jan 27, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- New Haven/Fed of teachers N. Haven, CT Feb 21, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- NY Ballet/ Local 802 AFM AAA NY, NY April 10, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- New England Horsemen's Benevolent & Protective Association, Inc. Feb 9, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Our Lady of Mercy/Local 1199 AAA NY March 15, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Pawtucket Nov 29, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Philadelphia/IAFF 22 AAA Phil. Feb 10, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Anderson Power/ UAW 1596 AAA Boston June 9, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Assoc. Spring (Barnes)/UAW 712 Bristol, CT (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Berkshire Medical/MNA Pittsfield, MA Jan 13, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Boston Sch Comm/Teachers Union AAA Boston Feb 1-3, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Triangle Wire/IBEW #1196 Seekonk, MA Jan 18, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- UPS/Teamsters 429 Phil, PA Jan 17, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- UPS/IBT 776 Phil, PA April 27, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- BU/SEIU 254 AAA Boston Feb 7, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Brookdale Hospital/Local 1199 NY, NY AAA March 21, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Buffalo Brd of Ed/Teachers Fed. Buffalo March 28, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Coca Cola/RWDSU #513 Andover, MA Marriott April 6, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Emery/Teamsters #25 AAA Boston Jan 11, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Emhart Glass/Local 376 UAW E. Hartford, CT AAA Jan 16, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Knights of Columbus/Local 153 New Haven. CT Dec 7, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Epsom Mediation Concord, NH Feb 16, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hartz MT/Bakery Drivers, 550 AAA NY Jan 31, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Keene Ed Assoc/NEA-NH School Board Feb 28, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Boston Edison/UWUA Back Bay Hilton March 1-2, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Portsmouth/FF Mediation Portsmouth City Hall Sept 15, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Public Service Electric/IBEW 94 Somerset, NJ May 3, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Raytheon Waltham Sept 1, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- RI Philharmonic/AFM Providence, RI Sept 18, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Shaw's/UFCW Braintree June 15 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Shaw's UFCW Local 791 Braintree, MA (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Scituate SC/Teachers Assoc. Scituate, MA May 4, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- SEIU 1199 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- SEIU vs. 1199 March 2, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Sony Music/Local 1212, IBEW Dec 5 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Beierdorf, Inc./USW 15536 Norwalk, CT June 14, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- HEB/BIU Bermuda June, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Bermuda Firefighters (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Hotel Employers Bermuda (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Commission on Competitiveness Final Report March, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Bermuda Hotels (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Bermuda, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Teknor Apex/IBT 64 Warwick, RI Oct 16, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- TBTA/BTOBA Interest Arbitration March & April, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- UPS/Teamsters 776 Harrisburg, PA Jan 23, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Warwick/IAFF 2748 Warwick, RI (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Western Mass Electric/IBEW 455 Holyoke, MA May 18, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- W. Warwick/AFSCME 94 N. Providence, RI Oct 30, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- AAA AFL-CIO (Box 5, Folder 5)
- WJAR/IBEW 1228 AAA Boston March 20, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- WJAR (Box 5, Folder 7)
- IRS and NTEU (Box 5, Folder 8)
- P & M Grievance, Boston Edison (Box 5, Folder 9)
- "Exhibit P" VHS; FDIC and NTEU (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Boston Edison - Local 369 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- IRS - NTEU (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Southampton Princess Hotel (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Bermuda Hotel (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Articles (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Prov. Journal/Newspaper Guild 41 Providence, RI (Box 6, Folder 6)
- SEIU Local 1984 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Interest Arbitration Rothschild (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Notes Misc. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- CBAs (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Hopkinton Public Schools Arbitration (folder 1 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Hopkinton Public Schools Arbitration (folder 2 of 2) (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Massachusetts (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Mass. House et al. (Box 7, Folder 4)
- State of Conn. and NEHCEU (Box 7, Folder 5)
- brief 1199 and Conn (Box 7, Folder 6)
- CBAs (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Conn (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Conn (continued) (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Conn Labor relations (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Nonotuck/SEIU Feb 22, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Re: Oral Reply (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Northeastern University/SEIU 254 AAA Boston Feb 15, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- City of Everett, IBPO City Hall Oct 3, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Lafayette School/Board of Ed SAU 35 Office June 28, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- City of Lynn/Police Assn. Oct 26, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Hopkington SD/MTA AAA Boston Sept 27-28, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- John Hancock/UFCW AAA Boston Oct 24, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- General Dynamics/ Groton, CT May 6, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- agreements, Booklets (Box 8, Folder 10)
- IRS Evidence (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Service Employees International Union, and District 1199 NE May 7, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Service Employees (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Re: SEIU and Local 1199NE Case No. 13-300-01510-93 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- VIA: Fax and First Class Mail Feb 25, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Official Proceedings April 20-23, 1992 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Re: National Treasury Employees Union and Federal Deposit Insurance Corporation (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Special Reports (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Healthcare Update, etc. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Service Employees International Union and District 1199 NE (Box 9, Folder 7)